Guide to the Amos Vogel Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Films, 1896-2001
  - Subseries II.1: Film Files, 1896-1993
    - Familie Nasdalko am Meer, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Family Life, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Family that Dwelt Apart, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Famu, The Film School, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Far From Vietnam, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Farrebique, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - The Fat and the Thin, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Fat Feet, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Fata Morgana, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Faust, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Faust ou Marguerite, 1960s (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Federmann und die SS, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - La Fee Sanguinaire, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Fellini, Federico (Articles About), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Une Femme Douce, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Fidel, undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - And the Fifth Horseman Is Fear, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Filet of Soul, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Une Fille et des Fusils, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Film Editing: Interpretations and Values, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Film, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Un Film, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Films of the 1890s, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Finally Got the News, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - A Finnish Fable, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Fireman's Ball, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - The Fire Walkers, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Fireworks, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - The First Charge of the Machete, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - First Love, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Fist in the Pocket, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - F For Fake, 1975-1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Five Abstract Film Exercises, 1943-1944 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Five Easy Pieces, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - 5 x Marilyn, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Flaming Creatures, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Flatland, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Flesh, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Flesh of Morning, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Flicker, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - The Flowers of St. Francis, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Flower Thief, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Fly, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - For the First Time, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Forbidden Games, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Forbidden Planet, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - For Example, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - For Example Bresson, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Form in Motion, undated (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Force of Evil, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - 481, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Au Fou!, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - The Four Hundred Blows, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Four in the Afternoon, 1950s (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Four Nights of a Dreamer, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - 491, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Four Stars, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Fragment of Seeking, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Frame-Up! The Imprisonment of Martin Sostre, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Francis Bacon, Paintings, 1944-1962, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Frank Film, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Freaks, 1932 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Free Radicals, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Freight Stop, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Frenzy, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Friction, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Fritz the Cat, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - From Lumiere to Langlois, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - From Morning to Midnight, 1922 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Fruits de Paradise, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Füf uns 1937, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Fuji, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Funeral Parade of Roses, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - The Further Adventures of Uncle Sam, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Fury, 1936 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Fuses, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Gabriel Under the White House, 1933 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Le Gai Savoir, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Games of Love, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - The Games of the Angels, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Gate of Hell, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Gates of Heaven, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - General Della Rovere, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Général Idi Amin Dada: Autoportrait, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - The General Line, 1926-1929 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Geography of the Body, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - German Dada, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Germany Awake, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Gestapoman Schmidt, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Ghosts Before Breakfast, 1927-1928 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - The Gibbons Moon, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - A Gift Town, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Gimme Shelter, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Gino's Pizza, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - A Girl in the Mist, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - The Girl With the Golden Eyes, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Giron (Bay of Pigs), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Give Peace a Chance, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - The Gladiators, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Glass, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Glen and Randa, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Glimpse of the Garden, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Glückselig, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - The Goalie's Anxiety at the Penalty Kick, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - The Go-Between, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - God Is Dog Spelled Backward, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - The Gods and the Dead, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Going Home, undated (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Going Places, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - The Golden Positions, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Der goldene Schuss, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Golden Years, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Der Golem, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Good Morning, 1960 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Good Night, Nurse, 1929 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - God Times, Wonderful Times, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Go Slow on the Brighton Line, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Goto, Island of Love, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Goto, Island of Love-- Poster (Box 15-K-5)
    - La Grande Bouffe, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Le Grand Melies, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Le Gran Siguriya, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Grease, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Gravity, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Great American Dream Machine, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - The Great Blondino, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - The Great Ecstasy of the Sculptor Steiner, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - The Great Society, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - The Great McGinty, 1940 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - The Greater Community Animal, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Greed, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Grierson, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - 1965 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - The Grim Reaper, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Groove Tube, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Groupies, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Guernica, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - La Guerre Est Finie, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Gymnopedies, undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Hail, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Hallelujah the Hills," 1963 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Hallucinations, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - The Hamburg, 1923 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Hamlet (Kosintser), 1964 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Hamlet, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - The Murder of Fred Hampton, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Hancock Airport, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - The Hand, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Hand-Held Day, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Hand Piece, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Hands Over the City, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Hands Up, 1926 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Handwritten, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Handy-Dandy Do It Yourself Animation Film, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Hanoi, Tuesday the 13th, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Hans Westmar, 1933 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Happiness, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Happy Anniversary, 1961 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Happy Working Class, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Harakiri, 1962 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Hard Day's Night, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - The Harder They Come, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Harlem Wednesday, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Harlan County USA, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Harry Munter, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Hasta la Victoria Siempre, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Have I Told You Lately That I Love You?, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Hawaiian Lullaby, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Hawks and Sparrows, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Heart of Glass, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Heat, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Heaven & Earth Magic, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Heavenly Star, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Heim Kehr, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - The Heirs, 1968-1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Hellzapoppin, 1941 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - The Hellstrom Chronicle, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Henry Miller Asleep and Awake, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Here Comes Every Body, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Hermes Bird, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Karl Hess: Toward Liberty, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - High, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - High School, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Highway, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Hi Mom, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Hiroshima-Nagasaki, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Hiroshima Mon Amour, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Hirshhorn, Joseph, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - His Marriage Wow, 1925 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Historia Naturae, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Historias de la Revolucion, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - History Lesson, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - History of the Blue Movie, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Hitler eine Karrier, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Hitler, A Film From Germany, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Hitlerjunge Quex, 1933 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Hog Calling Blues, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Hold Me While I'm Naked, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Holidays on Sylt, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - The Hollywood Cartoon (Film Series), 1974 (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Holy Ghost People, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Holy War, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Homage to Magritte, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Homage to Maybridge, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Homage to Jean Tinguely, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Des Hommes Dans le Ciel, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Honeymoon Hotel, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - The Hop Pickers, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Horror Dream, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Horse Over Tea Kettle, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Hospital, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Hotel Apex, 1952 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Hotel for Strangers, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - House, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - The House, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - The House Is Black, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - How To Be Loved, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Howard, undated (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Howard Smith Footage, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - How Could I Not Be Among You, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - How Much Wood Would A Woodchuck Chuck?, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - How Tasty Was My Little Frenchman, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - How To Make Love To A Nude Lady, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - H2O, 1929 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Hugo and Josephine, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Hugs and Kisses, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - The Human Condition, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Hummingbird, undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Hunger, undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Hunger, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - The Hunt (La Caza), 1966 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - The Hunters, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Hunting Scenes in Bavaria, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Hurry, Hurry, 1950s (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Hypnotic Behavior, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - I Am Pablo Neruda, 1970s (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - I Am Curious (blue), 1967 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Ice, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - I Change, I Remain the Same, undated (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Ich Bitte um's Wort, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - Ici et Ailleurs, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - The Idea, 1932 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - Identification Marks: None, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 43)
    - The Idyl, 1941 (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - I Even Met the Happy Gypsies, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - If…, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 46)
    - I. Stone's Weekly, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 47)
    - If the Wind Frightens You, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Igra, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 49)
    - Ikiru, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - I Love You, I Kill You, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - I Love You, Rosa, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Image in the Snow, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Images de la Folie, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Imagine, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - L'Imitation du Cinema, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - The Immigrant, 1917 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - L'Immortelle, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Immortal Story, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Inauguration of the Pleasure Dome, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - In Between, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - The Incredible Shrinking Man, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Robert Indiana Portrait, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - In the Happiness and Sorrow, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - L'Inhumaine, 1924 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - The Inner Scar, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Innocence Unprotected, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - The Innocent, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Innocent Sorcerers, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - An Inspector Comes, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Institutional Quality, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Interim, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Interplay, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Interview with Allende, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Interviews with My Lai Veterans, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Interview with Ambassador From Lapland, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - In the Company of Men, undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - In the Name of the Father, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - In the Realm of the Senses, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - In the Street, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Introspection, undated (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Intolerance, 1916 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Introduction to Accompaniment by Schoenberg, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Introduction to the Enemy, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - In the Year of the Pig, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Intimate Lighting, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Investigation of a Citizen Above Suspicion, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Invisible Opponents, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Invocation of My Demon Brother, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Ira, You'll Get Into Trouble, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Irreconcilable Memories, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Israel Why, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - ItalianAmerican, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - The Italian Straw Hat," 1927 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - It Happened Here, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - It Is Good to Live, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - It Is Not the Homosexual Who Is Perverse…, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - It's Not Just You, Murray!, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - It Was So Beautiful in Theresienstadt, 1944, 1964-1965 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Ivan The Terrible, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - I Walked With a Zombie, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - I Was a Kapo, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Izy Boukir, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Jabberwocky, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - J'Accuse, 1937 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Jail Keys Made Here, undated (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Jamestown Baloos," 1967 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Jammin' the Blues, 1944 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Jan Palach, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - The Japanese Sword, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Jaws, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Jazz Dance, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Jazz on a Summer's Day, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Jefferson Circus Songs, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Je T'Aime, Je T'Aime, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - La Jetee, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - La Joconde, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Johnnie Minotaur, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - The Joke, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Jonah Who Will Be 25 in the Year" 2000, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Jonas, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Josef Kilian, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Journey to Lithuania, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Joyce at 34, undated (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Joyless Street, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Judex, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Jud Süss, 1940 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - The Juggler of Our Lady, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Jules and Jim, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Jung Houston Film #1-#4, 1974, (4 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 43 to 46)
    - Junker der Waffen-SS, 1943 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - The Junk Playground, undated (Box 29, Folder 48)
    - Kathleen Ware, Quiltmaker, undated (Box 29, Folder 49)
    - Joszef Katús: Not Too Fortunate Return to the Land of Rembrandt, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 50)
    - Kaya, I'll Kill You, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 51)
    - Katzelmacher, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 52)
    - Buster Keaton Festival, 1917-1922 (Box 29, Folder 53)
    - Keaton Segment, 1910s (Box 29, Folder 54)
    - Khajuraho, undated (Box 29, Folder 55)
    - Kienholz on Exhibit, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 56)
    - King & Country, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 57)
    - King Joe, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 58)
    - King Kong, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 59)
    - Kings of the Road, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 60)
    - Kinoglaz, 1925 (Box 29, Folder 61)
    - Kirsa Nicholina, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - The Kiss, 1896 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Kiss, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Kiss, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Klinkaart, 1950s (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Klute, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - The Knack, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Knave of Hearts, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Matthias Kneissl, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Kodak Ghost Poems, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Kodak Ghost Poems Part II: False Pretenses, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Kodou, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Koestler on Creativity, 1970s (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Kolberg, 1945 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Kommando 52, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Koumiko Mystery, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Khrushchev, undated (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Yoji Kuri Retrospective, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Kustom Kar Kommandos, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Kwaidan, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Labyrinth, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Lacombe Lucien, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - The Lady Eve, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Lady of the Tracks, 1966 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Lady Vanishes, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - The Lady With the Little Dog, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Lafcadio, undated (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Lagerstrasse Auschwitz, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Lancelot of the Lake, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Land of Silence and Darkness, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Land without Bread, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - George Landow Retrospective, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Landscape, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Landscape After the Battle, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Langlois, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Language of Silence Cinema 1 & 2, undated (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Lapis, 1963-1967 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - The Last Laugh, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - The Last Millionaire, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - The Last of the Quevas, undated (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - The Last Picture Show, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Last Tango in Paris, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Last Words, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Last Year at Marienbad, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - The Late Matthew Pascal, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - LBJ, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Laughing Gravy, 1931 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - The Laughing Man, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - The Lead Shoes, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Lenny Bruce Without Tears, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Let Their Eyes Be Opened, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Letter to Jane, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Liberation of Mannique Mechanique, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - The Life, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Life and Death of a Hollywood Extra, 1928 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - A Life of the American Fireman, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - The Life of an American Fireman, 1903 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Life of Oharu, 1952 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Life Once Again, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Life with Video, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - A Light for John, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Lightening Waterfall Fern Soup, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Lineage, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Line of Apogee, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Lingo, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - The Lion Has Seven Heads, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Lions Love, 1969 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - The Lion Hunters, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Little Murders, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Lines of Firecrackers, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Living in a Reversed World, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Living the Good Life, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Lizzies of the Field, 1924 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Lola Montes, 1949 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Lonely Boy, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Long Live the Republic, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Long Pants, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - The Loneliness of the Long Distance Runner, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Loony Tom: The Happy Lover, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Lost in Cuddahy, undated (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Lot in Sodom, 1933 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Lotomania, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Louis Armstrong and Betty Boop, undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Louisiana Story, 1946-1948 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Love Affair (An Affair of the Heart), 1967 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Love and Anarchy, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Love in the City, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Love Goddesses, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Lovejoys Nuclear,War, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Lovemaking (Bartlett), 1970 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Lovemaking (Brakhage), 1969 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - The Lovers, 1958 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - The Love of Jeanne Ney, 1927 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Loves of a Blonde, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Loving, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Lucky Man, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Lucia, 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Lumiere, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Luminous Procuress, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - La Luna, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - A Luta Continua, 1960s (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Lysis, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - M, 1932 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Macbeth, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Macunaima, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Madeleine, Madeleine, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Magellan, 1972-1979 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Magical Death, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Magic Mountain, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Magic World of Karel Zeman, 1962 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - The Magnificent Ambersons, 1942 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Magritte, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Mahanager, 1963 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Maidanek, 1944 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Maidstone, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Les Maitres Fous, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Malcolm X, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Malcolm X Speaks, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Mama & Papa, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Mandabi, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Man From Onan, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - The Man He Might Have Been, 1913 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Man Is Not a Bird, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Mankinda, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Man of Aran, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Man of Wheat, undated (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Man Who Digs for Fish, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - The Man Who Left His Will on Film, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Man With a Movie Camera, 1929 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Man With Shaven Head, undated (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - The Man Who Lies, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 37)